Finding Aid for Topographic Quadrangle Maps, 1895-[ongoing].
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 15 Minute, Scale 1:62,500
  - Fairport-Manistee
    - Lansing N4230 W8430
      - Survey 1910; print 1912, green overprint
      - Survey 1910; print 1910; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Laughing Fish Point N4630 W8655
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Leonidas N4200 W8515
      - Survey 1917; print 1918, green overprint
      - Survey 1947; print 1950, green overprint
    - Lewiston N4445 W8415
      - Survey 1949; print 1949; reprint 1954, green overprint
    - Little Girls Point N4630 W9015
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Lowell N4245 W8515
      - Survey 1916; print 1918, green overprint
      - Survey 1916; print 1918; reprint 1950
    - Ludington N4345 W8615
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Luther N4400 W8530
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Mancelona N4445 W8500
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Manchester N4200 W8400
      - Survey 1948; print 1949, green overprint
      - Survey 1948; print 1948; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Manistee N4400 W8615
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1971, green overprint
  - Maple City-Schaffer
    - Maple City N4445 W8545 (Folder Maple City-Montague)
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Marcellus N4200 W8545
      - Survey 1944; print 1946
      - Survey 1944; print 1944; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Marenisco N4615 W8W930
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1961, green overprint
    - Marinette N4500 W8730
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Marion N4400 W8500
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Marquette N4630 W8715
      - Survey 1905; print 1907
      - Survey 1905; print 1907; reprint 1946
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Marshall N4215 W8445
      - Survey 1921; print 1923
      - Survey 1921; print 1923; reprint 1943
    - Mason N4230 W8415
      - Survey 1909; print 1911
      - Survey 1909; print 1911; reprint 1933
    - Matchwood N4630 W8W915
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Maumee Bay N4130 W8315
      - Survey 1899; print 1900; reprint 1909
    - Merrill N4315 W8415
      - Survey 1934; print 1937
      - Survey 1934; print 1934; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Mesick N4415 W8530
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Michigamme N4630 W8800
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1963, green overprint
    - Milford N4230 W8330
      - Survey 1908; print 1909
      - Survey 1908; print 1909; reprint 1950
    - Montague N4315 W8615
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Mt. Clemens N4230 W8245 (Folder Mt. Clemens-Onaway)
      - Survey 1926; print 1929
      - Survey 1926; print 1929; reprint 1950
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Mount Pleasant N4330 W8445
      - Survey 1916; print 1919, green overprint
      - Survey 1916; print 1919; reprint 1951
      - Survey 1916; print 1916; reprint 1972
    - Mullett Lake N4530 W8430
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Munising N4615 W8630
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Munising N4615 W8630
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1966
    - Muskegon N4300 W8600
      - Survey 1930; print 1936, green overprint
      - Survey 1930; print 1930; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Nashville N4230 W8500
      - Survey 1950; print 1951, green overprint
      - Survey 1950; print 1950; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - Ned Lake N4615 W8815
      - Survey 1895; print 1895
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1909
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1944
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Negaunee N4630 W8730
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Niles N4145 W8615
      - Survey 1927; print 1930
      - Survey 1927; print 1930; reprint 1950
      - Survey 1927; print 1927; reprint 1966
    - North Ironwood N4630 W9000
      - Survey 1956; print 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - North Manitou N4500 W8555
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Northland N4600 W8730
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Northport N4500 W8530
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Norway N4545 W8745
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Onaway N4515 W8400
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Onekama N4415 W8600 (Folder Onekama-Rapid River)
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Ontonagon N4645 W8W915
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Otsego Lake N4445 W8430
      - Survey 1949; print 1949; reprint 1954, green overprint
    - Passage Island N4800 W8815
      - Survey1895 print 1895
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1909
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1933
    - Pelkie N4645 W8830
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Pellston N4530 W8445
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Pembine N4530 W8745
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1970, green overprint
    - Peninsula Point N4530 W8645
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Perch Lake N4615 W8830
      - Survey 1895; print 1895
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1909
      - Survey 1895; print 1895; reprint 1925
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Perrinton N4300 W8430
      - Survey 1916; print 1918, green overprint
    - Petoskey N4515 W8445
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Phelps N4600 W8W900
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - Pioneer N4130 W8430
      - Survey 1911; print 1914, green overprint
      - Survey 1911; print 1914; reprint 1941
    - Plymouth N4215 W8315
      [earlier edition titled Wayne]
      - Survey 1903; print 1905; reprint 1932
    - Pontiac N4230 W8315
      - Survey 1906; print 1907
      - Survey 1906; print 1907; reprint 1912
      - Survey 1906; print 1907; reprint 1918
      - Survey 1906; print 1907; reprint 1937
    - Portland N4245 W8445
      - Survey 1945; print 1946, green overprint
    - Powers N4530 W8730
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Ralph N4600 W8745
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Rapid River N4545 W8645
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Ravenna N4300 W8545 (Folder Ravenna-Schaffer)
      - Survey 1945; print 1947
      - Survey 1945; print 1945; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Reed City N4345 W8530
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Republic N4615 W8745
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Rives Junction N4215 W8415
      - Survey 1919; print 1921, green overprint
      - Survey 1919; print 1921; reprint 1948
      - Survey 1919; print 1919; reprint 1960
    - Rochester N4230 W8300
      - Survey 1906; print 1908
      - Survey 1906; print 1908; reprint 1936
    - Rock N4600 W8700
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Rockland N4630 W8W900
      - Survey 1949; print 1951
      - Survey 1949; print 1949; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1949; print 1949; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Romulus N4200 W8315
      - Survey 1903; print 1906
      - Survey 1903; print 1906; reprint 1915
        [in Detroit folio only]
      - Survey 1903; print 1906; reprint 1926
    - Rousseau N4630 W8845
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Saginaw N4315 W8345
      - Survey 1916; print 1919, green overprint
    - Sagola N4600 W8800
      - 1895;, 1899
      - 1895;, 1899; reprint 1913
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
    - St. Charles N4315 W8400
      - Survey 1914; print 1917, green overprint
      - Survey 1914; print 1917; reprint 1950
    - Saline N4200 W8345
      - Survey 1902; print 1906
      - Survey 1902; print 1906; reprint 1929, green overprint
    - Sand Lake N4315 W8530
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Sanford N4330 W8415
      - Survey 1934; print 1936, green overprint
      - Survey 1934; print 1934; reprint 1965
    - Sault Ste. Marie N4615 W8415
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Schaffer N4545 W8715
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1965, green overprint
  - SchoolCraft-Ypsilanti
    - Schoolcraft N4200 W8530 (Folder Schoolcraft-Swanton)
      - Survey 1920; print 1922
      - Survey 1920; print 1922; reprint 1950
    - Shelldrake N4630 W8500
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Shepherd N4330 W8430
      - Survey 1930; print 1936
      - Survey 1930; print 1930; reprint 1961, green overprint
      - Survey 1930; print 1930; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Shingleton N4615 W8615
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Sidnaw N4630 W8830
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Skandia N4615 W8700
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Skanee N4645 W8800
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - South Fox Island N4515 W8545
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - South Haven N4215 W8615
      - Survey 1927; print 1930, green overprint
      - Survey 1927; print 1930; reprint 1948
    - South Lyon N4215 W8330
      - Survey 1902; print 1906
      - Survey 1902; print 1906; reprint 1944
      - Survey 1902; print 1902; reprint 1954
    - Spring Arbor N4200 W8430
      - Survey 1948; print 1949
    - Springport N4215 W8430
      - Survey 1919; print 1921, green overprint
      - Survey 1919; print 1919; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1919; print 1919; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Starlake N4600 W8W915
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Stephenson N4515 W8730
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Steuben N4600 W8615
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1967, green overprint
    - Stockbridge 4215; 8400
      - Survey 1919; print 1922, green overprint
      - Survey 1919; print 1919; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Strongs N4615 W8445
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1958, green overprint
    - Swanton N4130 W8345
      - Survey 1911; print 1914, green overprint
      - Survey 1911; print 1914; reprint 1937
      - Survey 1911; print 1911; reprint 1956, green overprint
    - Tawas City N4415 W8330 (Folder Tawas City-Washington Island)
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Thayer N4615 W8W915
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Thomaston N4630 W8W945
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1961, green overprint
    - Thompsonville N4430 W8545
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Three Oaks N4145 W8630
      - Survey 1927; print 1930
      - Survey 1927; print 1930; reprint 1946
    - Three Rivers N4145 W8530
      - Survey 1914; print 1916, green overprint
      - Survey 1914; print 1916; reprint 1932
      - Survey 1914; print 1914; reprint 1956
      - Survey 1914; print 1914; reprint 1966
    - Toledo N4130 W8330
      - Survey 1899; print 1900; reprint 1909
    - Tower N4515 W8415
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Traverse City N4445 W8530
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Trenary N4600 W8645
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Twin Lake N4315 W8600
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Union City N4200 W8500
      - Survey 1917; print 1918, green overprint
      - Survey 1947; print 1950, green overprint
      - Survey 1947; print 1947; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Vandalia N4145 W8545
      - Survey 1945; print 1948
      - Survey 1948; print 1949, green overprint
      - Survey 1948; print 1948; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1948; print 1948; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Wakefield N4615 W8W945
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Washington Island N4515 W8645
      - Survey 1960; print 1960; reprint 1962, green overprint
    - Watersmeet N4615 W8W900 (Folder Watersmeet-Ypsilanti)
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Watson N4600 W8715
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Wausaukee N4515 W8745
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Wauseon N4130 W8400
      - Survey 1911; print 1913, green overprint
      - Survey 1911; print 1911; reprint 1954
    - Wayland N4230 W8530
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Wayne N4215 W8315
      [later edition titled Plymouth]
      - Survey 1903; print 1905
      - Survey 1903; print 1905; reprint 1915
    - Wellston N4400 W8545
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - White Cloud N4330 W8545
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - White Pine N4645 W8W930
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1956; print 1956; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Winona N4645 W8845
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Witbeck N4615 W8800
      [later edition titled Witch Lake]
      - Survey1896 print 1899
      - Survey 1896; print 1899; reprint 1950
    - Witch Lake N4615 W8800
      [earlier edition titled Witbeck]
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1957, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1959, green overprint
    - Wolverine N4515 W8430
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1958, green overprint
      - Survey 1957; print 1957; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Wood Island N4630 W8630
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1969, green overprint
    - Woodville N4330 W8530
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Wyandotte N4200 W8300
      - Survey 1904; print 1906
      - Survey 1904; print 1906; reprint 1915
    - Ypsilanti N4200 W8330
      - Survey 1902; print 1906
      - Survey 1902; print 1902; reprint 1958
  - Described above (Folder 1)
- 15 Minute, Scale 1:48,000
  - Cedar Springs N4300 W8530 (Folder 1:48,000)
    - Survey 1916
  - De Witt N4245 W8430
    - Survey 1921
    - Survey 1925
  - Durand N4245 W8345
    - Survey 1920; print 1921
  - Flint N4300 W8330
    - Survey 1920; print 1921
  - Holly N4245 W8330
    - Survey 1920; print 1921
  - Marshall N4215 W8445
    - Survey 1921
  - Montague N4315 W8615
    - Survey 1929
  - Muskegon N4300 W8600
    - Survey 1928
  - Schoolcraft N4200 W8530
    - Survey 1920; print 1921
  - Shepherd (South Half) N4330 W8430
    - Survey 1929
  - Stockbridge N4215 W8400
    - Survey 19Survey 19
  - Twin Lake (South Half) N4315 W8600
    - Survey 1929
    - Survey 1929; print 1930; reprint 1949
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:24,000
  - Adair - Cutlerville
    - Adair 42082G6 (Folder Adair-Algonac)
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Adams Point 45083D6
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Addison 41084H3
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Adrian 41084H1
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1963, green overprint
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1979; photorevised, green overprint
    - Afton 45084C4
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Ahmeek 47088C4
      - Survey 1946; print 1947
      - Survey 1946; print 1947; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1946; print 1947; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1946; print 1946; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Alabaster 44083B5
      - Survey 1966; print 1966; reprint 1968
      - Survey 1966; print 1966; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Alamando 43084F5
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Alba 44084H8
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Albany Island 45084H1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Alberta 46088F4
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Alcona Dam Pond 44083E7
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Aldridge Creek 46089F6
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Alfred 46087A6
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Algonac 42082E5
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Alicia 43084C1 (Folder Alicia-Ann Arbor West)
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Allen 41084H7
      - Survey 1960; print 1960; reprint 1961, green overprint
      - Survey 1960; print 1960; reprint 1977; photorevised, green overprint
    - Allendale 42085H8
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1959, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Allenton 42082H8
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Alma North 43084D6
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Alma South 43084C6
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Almont 42083H1
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Alpena 45083A4
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Alto 42085G4
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979, green overprint
    - Altona 43085E3
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Alvordton 41084F4
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Amasa 46088B4
      - Survey 1945; print 1947
      - Survey 1945; print 1945; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Anderson Lake 46087B4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Ann Arbor East 42083C6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ann Arbor West 42083C7
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Applegate 43082C6 (Folder Applegate-Auger Lake)
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Argyle 43082E8
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Armada 42082G8
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Arnold 46087A4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Arthur Bay 45087C4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Ashley 43084B4
      - Survey 1974; print 1974; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Assumption 41083F8
      - Survey 1960; print 1960; reprint 1971; photorevised, green overprint
    - Atlanta 45084A2
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint